Thank you for watching
me
flying high garmen
Ahhhh!
Idols whose faces are the most important part of their lives are now competing against each other in various competitions using only their faces in team competitions.
Tonight we continue the game where you have to make a cute face once every 10 seconds.
You can make a cute face if you eat a lot of shaved ice in a minute.
But the syrup makes it heavier, so we'll be very strict about spilling it.
Okay then...
No!
It feels good to eat 3 boo-boos down!
You can hold it when you eat it.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
That's good, that's good, that's good. Shaved ice.
You can't go any further than that.
Back, back, back, back.
Back, back, back.
Six. Five. Four.
Don't spill it.
Three.
Two people continue to eat with the least amount of food.
Then, the one-minute fast-eating time is over.
First, Mr. Himura, the chairman of the judging committee, strictly checks the food over the trip.
Do you want to add a little more?
It's just a little more than that.
Because this is a competition.
It's a tough game.
She's really good.
This one's really good, too.
320 grams.
The difference between the two is 10 grams. As a result, the difference between the two was 10 grams.
From here, it's time to judge the difference.
But this will add 10 grams to the minus.
That's right.
Okay, let's start here.
First one.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's cute.
Let's go to the second one.
Okay.
That's the one.
Go on.
What do you think? Endo, this one.
It's from 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜.
Oh, well, it's cute.
Go on, then.
Oh, 〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜〜
Matsuo's been doing this for a while.
I want to go that far.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
You're making too many faces.
If you do it again, you'll get in trouble.
That's right.
And the pea... it's okay if he's tongue-tied.
The tongue was good.
What do you mean "good tongue"?
It's a good pattern.
Go on.
Hey!
That's what I thought.
Next is the last one. Matsuo's winning by 10 grams.
Last one.
Oh, Matsuo!
There was another piece, wasn't there? Matsuo, you can't do this.
No, he had the first piece. Tough.
The same pose as before.
What?
I have it. I have it, same pose.
Your face is different.
Because the expression on your face is different.
Different faces.
The piece has a different face.
Okay, this one's good.
The rock team wins this showdown.
They're saying a lot.
A little too much.
They're saying how cute and adorable you are!
Team Iwa, you're so loud!
Team rock minus 3 azukis.
Three adzukis?
When they say "3 azukis," let's all shuffle along.
Next, Shibata and Kubo spin around in a chair.
How's Shibata?
Very good at it.
You use that in rhythmic gymnastics?
He's strong.
Kubo, how's your spinning?
I'm weak for the first three and a half periods.
I'm weak in this competition, too.
That's why I'm wondering if I can be pretty.
But if I'm chosen, no matter how good or bad I am... this won't change.
I'll do my best.
Well then, let's go!
Let's get started!
12345678
That's not going to change.
But I guess this is the second half.
1091010
Is the number of revolutions the same?
Last one Last
Niigata's Kubo operates with an unexpected dive pastel
The one-minute record is
Yes, it's over!
Kubo was surprisingly fast!
Kubo was faster than Shibata... 26 laps.
Kubo's 29 laps... and still ahead of Shibata in RPMs.
I'll take that as a "yes".
I'm not sure we'll get a turnaround.
Oh, this is what I'm talking about.
Let's be strict about the same moves.
Kubo's looking a little pained.
Kubo's looking a little distressed.
I saw the camera.
Next... cute.
Kubo's doing a great job.
And the fifth one... That one's strong.
That one's okay. The last one...
Cute!
Shibata, what do you think? I don't like it. That's why I stopped.
I'll get a lot of flak from the judges.
That's right. They say I'm cute, cute, cute.
So this one's okay, too. We'll confirm the winner here, too.
The rock team wins!
Are you tired, Mr. Himuro? My knee hurts.
You have water in your knee, Mr. Himuro? No problem at all.
Let's play the next game, Mr. Himuro.
"Magao Gambar." - "Magao Gambar.
"Magao Gambar." - "Magao Gambar." - "Magao Gambar.
You talk one-on-one about a subject.
During the game, you take a picture of your opponent's face at any time you like.
The winner is the one who can shoot Magao first!
First, Yoda and Mukai face off to see who can crack the other's smile.
Talk about your favorite food.
Let's go for a gun bar start!
What do you think?
What do you think? What?
It's for you.
Wait, there's so many things.
Before this...
This one's good.
Se-ne-te...
Dumplings.
You both like gyoza?
Is there anything you don't like?
Okay... food you don't like.
Yes, I do.
Seino.
Shrimp.
Uh...
What's not to like?
What do you hate about shrimp?
I don't like shrimps.
Tell me what you don't like about shrimp.
The way they look, the way they taste, the way they smell.
It's all a big muddy mess.
My pet peeve is the stink bugs.
I know.
Are they stinkbugs?
Are you a stink bug?
You like stink bugs?
I hate them.
Not many people like stinkbugs.
Two minutes elapsed.
Oh, man.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'll stop you right there.
This is it.
No?
He's laughing. He's laughing.
He's laughing, he's laughing, he's laughing.
I'm going to put this in the poofing and laughing category.
He's smiling. - He's smiling.
He's laughing, he's laughing, he's laughing. This is it, this is what I'm laughing at.
He's smiling.
He's washing the corners of his mouth.
From now on, we're going to go from gray to black around here.
These areas are already black.
This is the first time.
Okay, let's continue.
Okay, okay.
What?
What's the one ingredient you can't miss?
Chives and garlic.
Chives, garlic...
Yuzu kosho?
Yoda, Yoda, Yoda, Yoda...
No, no, no...
What do you think?
He's smiling.
Here's the other one, too.
Why?
So, Mukai succeeded in hitting it too!
The rock team won!
Mukai is asking a question, too.
Yoda came up with the idea.
Mukai's so good!
And Mukai is smiling with his teeth all the time.
I'm used to seeing his mouth like this when he's playing around in the field.
I was scared because he was talking like this the whole time.
Next was Kuromi and Kubo.
The topic of the talk was "Favorite movie".
Let's say it together!
But we were together before, weren't we?
We were together before.
Se-no!
That's totally different.
Is that a lie?
Kuromi...
Kuromi didn't like it.
But I know what you were going to say. But I get what you were trying to say.
It's the Samurai Japan one, right?
What's your favorite part?
I think it was when he was shot.
Who is it?
But isn't that right, Mr. Laiki?
The part where he was shot.
The scene where he's crying.
I want you to see that.
The scene with Genda...
Genda's surprise.
Where?
Even with a broken bone.
Even with a broken bone, he's willing to keep going.
Nakano's action at that time was also good.
I liked what he did, too.
It was great to see how the Samurai Japan team works together.
We've got to get him away from baseball.
Where was your favorite makeup scene?
Yoshida's three-run homer.
You know... there was that one.
It's not about baseball.
I saw it during a previous project.
I recommended "What's your name?
I've seen it.
I told you until the end.
No, not until halfway through.
I don't remember.
Do you have any recommendations?
When you were one half.
When she's on the other side.
This one.
This crop.
Oh, my God!
That's a little bit...
That's not good.
It's a little too close to the opinion.
You said it was time for a split. You said it was time to split up.
This is it.
It's all over.
The winner is Kubo.
Clove, you've been on the attack for a long time.
It's time to split!
That one time!
At the other end...
What do you think?
In the third round, Hayashi vs. Tamura, can you shut down your opponent's movie?
The topic for you two is "Three-letter word game.
Answer with three letters.
Oh, no!
Let's go!
Let's start!
Let's start from the forest's side.
Which one first?
I'll go first.
Shizuku
a drop of water
car
everywhere in the city
and
mountain and mountain goats
lizard
Fu
I don't care if you take those dept. points or whatever.
hmm
(Japanese word for "fukka")
hmm...
Oh, wait a minute.
Let's try it again.
Oh no!
This forest is already this
Hime-chan
You say "Fukka", right?
This is funka, right?
If you look closely, though, you can see the effect is rising. If you look closely, though, you can see that the effect has improved.
Let's continue.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
Where do I start?
I'll tell you...
exclaim
.......................
I'm sorry, this is a little
a little
He's laughing.
Lu's smile
Is that a smile, Lu?
What do you think?
If you look very close, she's smiling like this.
I'm going to play it safe.
Be careful, Lin!
Hayashi, you can't do it again!
But then again, I keep missing Hayashi, the weakest player in the game.
Hayashi?
Bugle, pants, tsumiki.
No, no, no, no, no!
Here it is!
So the rock team wins again.
That's 2... that's 2...
And now, for the overwhelmingly outnumbered Yama team
Finally, a special rescue game!
If one person from the mountain team can make a funny face in 30 seconds and make the other team laugh, they get a point.
If you win 2 out of 3 challenges, you get a chance to tie the game.
First, Umezawa took on the challenge
Make Kaki of the Iwa team laugh!
Start the game!
What is the face you made in 30 seconds?
Mr. Himura, please be careful not to get too close or you may laugh at him.
Here we go!
Three, two, one.
Yes, sir.
Are you sure this is safe? Are you saying this is safe?
You don't think it's safe?
That's a tough one.
That's what it looks like.
The mountain team with no trace is challenged by Hayashi.
Can you make the guy across from you laugh?
Three, two, one.
This is amazing.
Laughter
Yes, clear
This is not over.
Clear.
I attacked it, but it's too early.
That was close.
We've lost the chance to win, but we're going to try again with Kuromori, just in case.
Can you make it to the end?
Three, two, one.
Fast forward.
Boober...
boooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Boob-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah.
It's a game of punishment, isn't it?
Boo-boo!
What is it this time?
I heard that you can do anything you want.
I'm going to use electricity on your face...
The moment we connect our cheeks, the electricity will flow from our cheeks.
Boo-boo!
If you want to make a cheek, just make a cheek and it will go boom.
I'm scared of this, right?
The other one goes there... so those two are important.
You have to be brave.
Wait a minute, they're going... wait a minute, they're going... they're going now... but they're captains...
No, but I'm the captain.
No, but I'm the captain of the whole team.
Boobar!
I'm the captain of the whole team. Yes, sir.
The order was quietly decided, but then it all came to an unbelievable end.
Stop AIMing.
After 15,000 volts of current has been stored, it's time to start the most punishing game of all.
I see a line of people...
What's going on? What's going on?
I'm not in the mountains!
Why are you here?
One at a time!
So Kyuukyu Himura will be punished together
It's okay, guys.
You must be scared
Now you're waiting for Sensei Ume with her cheeks on
You won't come when I put them on?
I'm sure she won't.
They shouldn't.
Shall we go now?
Wait, wait.
Why does he keep trying?
I'm scared.
That's what I'm afraid of.
Stop it!
I'm so scared.
It's not coming.
Not at the plum stage, huh?
I'm afraid of the plums, aren't I?
I'll go.
Oh, no!
I'm scared
Look, look.
They're all oohing and aahing over here, too.
Oh, my God.
This is scary.
Are the plums on?
Not yet.
I'm afraid to put these on, too. I'm afraid to even put this on.
Like this one's not coming.
It's not coming.
Okay, Yamashita.
I'm scared.
When Yamashita puts his cheek on it, it goes to everyone.
They're all very clever.
Okay, then.
Shall we go, Yamashita?
I'm scared.
Make up your mind, everyone.
I didn't know Mr. Himuro was in.
Why am I in here?
Why am I in?
I can't do it anymore if you're gone.
Thanks for that.
Shall we go?
Yamashita.
I'm counting on you.
Don't worry.
We can go at once.
Take your time.
About 10 cm to go.
I'm sure.
We'll all go together.
Who's up?
Okay.
One.
Ouch.
Ouch!
First of all, is Yamashita Ume okay?
Ouch! Ouch.
My face is cracked.
Your face is broken.
Your face is totally normal and cute.
Two on the face works.
It's like...
It's like, "Oh, no, it's gone through.
It's going through the face.
I could feel something flowing.
Oh, there it goes.
Wait, but... when everyone was falling down...
I was just doing this to myself.
Tsutsuki was fine.
The pressure hurt.
I'm not so sure if it was strong.
My feet are burned... and my face...
I see.
Endo, how did it go?
Here.
Mr. Himuro, I have the silver one.
Hurry, hurry, take it.
Yuno-san's changed.
The lights have gone on, she's changed.
What's going on?
She's here. She's here.
She's here, she'll sneak it to me tonight.
Is my palm growing?
What do you mean?
I've never seen lines like this.
This is bad.
Only on Mr. Himura's side.
This is bad!
Umme and Yuukyan Yamashita...
I got hit.
I know, I know.
What the hell, a Sunday theater guy...
I'm not getting my face ripped off. I'm not gonna get my face ripped off.
All right, well, let's do a second round, shall we?
You're not going to do it.
Why are we going for a second shot?
It's like it never happened.
Mr. Yamashita, if you're going to do it...
What?
What are you talking about?
That's right.
I'll do the second one.
You two in the middle.
No, no, no, no. Why am I in?
They want me to be in it.
I don't care if we're on the far end.
What are you doing?
Why are you being so flippant towards me?
You two are in the middle.
Lilting extended battle
We're in.
How can you do it again, cheeks?
Why?
I want to try
In the middle.
What's wrong with you?
This isn't that kind of show!
Hey, Mr. Himuro, you can't lose.
No, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
I don't get it.
Let's go in the middle, with the guy who puts his cheeks on.
Mr. Himuro.
Me?
I'll do it.
It's so unfair!
Himuro-san, say it. Say Himuro-san!
Let's see what's different about this year's Nogizaka.
All right, everyone, we're going to do the chattering.
321.
Super scary!
No, this is for real.
What am I going to do?
Why are you doing this?
What if we're trapped? What if we're trapped?
I don't know!
I'll be the only one embarrassed the moment the lights come on.
You want to do it, so everyone else does it, too.
I'm so scared!
Why are you doing this?
I'm scared.
I won't stop.
Let's not do it, let's not do it.
It's too scary!
Don't waste your time.
Himawawa-san, put your hands on your hips.
It's all right here, isn't it?
Yes, it's all right there.
I'm scared.
Yes, I'm scared.
Kaho.
Kaho...
Kaho, you keep kissing me.
It's not nice, but...
I don't mind.
I'm not gonna do it.
Can I talk to you once?
Just once.
Sorry. - That's a little scary, right? Oh, my God.
I don't know how you guys do it.
It's too scary.
I'm scared.
I'm soaking wet from nerves. I'm soaking wet from nerves, I hope you're okay, doctor.
I'm fine. It's more fluid.
It's bad.
Oh, my God, I'm so nervous!
I shouldn't have said that.
Have Himawa put it on.
Okay, then.
Tell me when you're going, and do the countdown.
So you're okay with 321?
Seriously, he's too strong.
I'm scared.
That's scary.
Even if I do it once, I'm still scared.
I'm scared.
I'll do it with the whole staff next time.
Oh, man, I'm scared.
Okay, then.
I'm scared.
Can we all do it together?
Let's count down.
Okay.
Three.
Two.
One.
Ow, that hurts.
Ow!
Ow.
I'm serious.
It's so bad, it's knocking me right in the face.
Why are you doing this?
How was it, Yura?
I was like, "For real, when Mr. Yamai said that, he punched me in the face!
I was standing on the tube again!
Why is she doing this?
It's terrifying.
It happened with a snap. It happened with a snap.
He's doing "Aru Aru Tankentai.
You fainted!
It's amazing how strong and weak the electricity is.
Grandmas don't really feel it.
Young people feel it.
I'm a grandma!
I'm a grandma.
She says she's a grandma.
11th year birthday live
The jacket photo of the Blu-ray & DVD of the 11th year birthday live is ready!
Second round of mobile selection for birthday live starts today!
Tickets for UnderLive streaming viewing are now on sale!
This is Tamami Sakaguchi.
In 2024, I'll be working with Kubo Toreno and the three of us.
I would like to do a live performance of us as adults
I would like to do it somewhere.
So everyone, please subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel.